Guide to the Foote, Cone & Belding Communications, Inc. Records, 1964-1978 and undated RL.00405
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Scripts, 1977 and undated, 301491; 2 boxes
  - FCB Tape 8, originals with index, undated, 301503 (Box 4)
    [includes Agree Creme Rinse, Alcohol Studies, Alexander Ford, Alka Seltzer, Allstate, Anacin, Agricultural Chemicals, American Animal Protection Society, Avon, BC Powders, Beach Music, Bic Lighter, Bic Shaver, Carowinds, Cheap Joe's Jeans, Clairol Hairdryers, Conor Mobile Homes, Cover Girl, Crisco, Cutex, Drano, Ex Lax, Fit and Trim Dog Food, Food Safety, Ford Lincoln Versaille, Ford Pick-up Trucks, Freshen-Up Gum, General Motors, General Telephone, Glade Solid, Hellman's Mayonnaise, Housing Discrimination, Kellogg's, Kool-Aid, Mazola Margarine, Milk Bone Dry Biscuits, Muscular Dystrophy, National Guard, Nestea, Oscar Mayer, Phillips Petroleum, Pillsbury Figurines, Pillsbury No Bake Pies, Raintree Moisturizers, Red Cross, Revlon, Ruby (movie), Saturday Night Live, Schick Blades, Sears, Shout, Sip Stick, Smith-Corona Typwriters, Tender Vittles Cat Food, Tickle Anti-Perspirant, Top Choice Dog Food, Transouth Mortgage, Ultra Bright Toothpaste, U.S. Air Force, Vitalis, Water Pik Shower Massage, Wild Turkey Society, Winn Dixie, Wisk, Wrangler Jeans and Cotton, Wygul Ford, Yellow Pages]
  - FCB Tape 9, originals with index, undated, 301502 (Box 4)
    [Includes Adolph's Meat Tenderizer, Alka Seltzer Plus, Arrid XX, Arthritis Bufferin, Arthritis Pain Formula, Ajax Cleaner, Ban, Bayer, Bounce, Chiffon Margarine, Coast Soap, Cold Powder XEE, CoTylenol, Coffee Mate, Comet, Crest, Crisco Oil, Cycle Dog Food, Dawn Soap, Duncan Hines, Eggs, Excedrin P.M., Fab, Fem Iron, Final Net, Florida, Freezone Corn Remover, Gain, Good Seasons, Green Giant Corn, Hanes Pantyhose, Heinz Gravy, Hi-C Orange Drink, Hold Cough Suppressant, Hormel Chili, Ivory Liquid, Jiff, Johnson's Baby Lotion, Kal Kan Cat Food, Keebler Crackers, Kraft, Lava Soap, Libby's, Log Cabin Pancakes, Lovin' Spoonfuls, Metamucil, Milk Bone, Mrs. Goodcookie, Mrs. Paul's Fish Food, Nestle's Soup, Northern Towels, One-A-Day Vitamins, Ora-gel, Pampers, Pamprin, Pine State Milk, Playtex, Prell Concentrate, Pringle's Potato Chips, Purina Dog Food, Quaker Oats, Ragu Spaghetti Sauce, Reach Toothbrush, Ruffles, Scott Towels, Secret Anti-Perspirant, Shake 'n Bake, Snackin' Cake, Sominex, Spray 'n Wash, Star Magazine, Sure, Swiss Miss Cocoa, Tang, Timex, Tone Soap, Top Choice, Tuck's, Windex, Wisconsin Vegetables, Wyler's Fruit Drink, Zest, Zip-loc Bags]
  - FCB Tape 12, originals with index, undated, 301501 (Box 4)
    [Includes Bar-S Franks, Clairol Foot-fixer, Fire Prevention, First National Bank of Chicago, Foster Farm's Chicken Franks, Hallmark, Hunt's Reddi-Wip, Knudsen Cottage Cheese, Mazda (vs. Rabbit), Sears, Sherwin-Williams Paint, Sweetheart Bread, Tone Soap, Tropical Blend Suntan Lotion, United California Bank, Valley Bank, Western Electric]
  - FCB Tape 13, originals with index, undated, 301500 (Box 4)
    [Includes 409 Spray Cleaner, Albertson's Supermarkets, Arizona Biltmore, C and H Sugar, California Raisins, Circle-K Food Stores, Clean and Clear, Clorox II, Crave Cat Food, Cudahy Extra Lean Hotdogs, Dole Pineapple, First National Bank of Chicago, Fritos, Frost 'n Tip, Girard Bank, Hallmark, Heinz Deep Fries, Home Savings, Idaho Potatoes, Levi's Dura Plus, Milkmate, Pacific Telephone Directory Assistance, Reddi-Wip, Sears, Sherwin-Williams Paint, Shout, Speed Queen Dryer, Soft Scrub, Sunkist Oranges, Twice as Fresh Air Freshener, Western Electric, Winchell's Doughnuts]
  - FCB Tape 17, originals without index, undated, 301499 (Box 4)
    [Includes Arizona Mining Association, Bank of Nevada, C and H Pure Kane Sugar, Campbell's Soups, Clairol, Clorox, Equitable Life Insurance, Emigrant Bank, Frito's, Hallmark, Hughes Airwest Airlines, Kraft, Las Vegas Hilton, Lestoil, Levis, Mazda, Mealtime Dog Food, Miss Clairol, Prevention of Forest Fires, Sears, Sherwin Williams, Sunbeam, United California Bank, Valley National Bank, Western Electric Telephones]
  - FCB Tape 20 (NYVI), originals with index, undated, 301498 (Box 4)
    [Includes Clairol, Fritos, Lestoil, Sears, Western Electric]
  - FCB Tape 21, originals with index, undated, 301497 (Box 4)
    [Includes Be-Fresh Toilet Bowl Cleaner, Clean Sweep Rug Cleaner, Dial Deodorant Soap, Future Floor Shine, Johnson Wax, Scrunge Tough Steel Scouring Pad, Shout Laundry Pretreat Detergent]
  - Miscellaneous, undated, 301496 (Box 4)
    [Includes Clearasil Skin Care, Irish Spring Soap, Noxzema Skin Cream]
  - SFF1, handwritten without index, undated, 301495 (Box 4)
    [C and H Brown Sugar, C and H Pure Kane Sugar, California Raisins, Dole Pineapple, Idaho Potatoes, Long Distance (Cheaper Rates), Tone Soap]
  - SFF1, originals with index, undated, 301494 (Box 4)
    [Includes 409 Cleanser, C and H Sugar, California Raisins, Clorox, Dole Pineapple, Idaho Potatoes, Pacific Telephone, Soft Scrub, Tone Soap, Twice as Fresh]
  - SFF2, handwritten with index, undated, 301493 (Box 4)
    [Includes Clorox, Levi's]
  - SFF2, originals with index, undated, 301492 (Box 4)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1976-1979 and undated, 301441; 3 boxes
  Arranged to mirror the organization of scripts. Where available, content lists have been transcribed for relevant items.
  - Series A: CHF1 034-061, CHR3 106-149. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301490 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 1. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301489 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 2. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301488 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 3. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301487 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 4. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301486 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 5. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301485 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 6. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301484 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 7. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301483 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 8. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301482 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 9. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301481 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 10. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301480 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 11. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301479 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 12--Domestic Reel 2nd Q77. 1977. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301478 (Box AV1)
    [Chicago: First National Bank (Swiss Watch); Hallmark (Carousel, Prelude, Gift Center #2); ISC (Americana Sweetheart); Sears (Back, Tires); Sherwin-Williams (Eight Years)]
    [Jennings & Thompson: Valley National Bank (Antique Dealer, Why Not Trade It In?); Cudahy Foods (Cud Cudahy Western Character, Smokey Western Flavor)]
    [Los Angeles: United California Bank (Cash Register); U.S. Forest Service (Only You, I Think I Love You Smokey singing spot); United California Bank (Silver Dollars); Mazda (Rabbit); Knudson Dairy Products (Cottage Cheese animated spot); Mazda (Vs. Honda); United California Bank (Falling Bill); Reddi Wip (Eikes, Yikes)]
    [New York: Sears (Pop Ons, Little Old Ladies Rev., Working Man, Blazers); Western Electric (Describe a Phone, 3 A.M., Blue Danube); Foot Fixer (Feel Good); Plough (Girl in Jungle)]
    [San Francisco: Armour Dial Tone Soap (Tennis); Foster Farms Chicken Franks (Julie, Adam)]
  - FCB 13--4th Quarter 1977 compilation reel. 1977. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301477 (Box AV1)
    [Aitkin Kynett: Girard Bank (Money Game)]
    [Chicago: First National Bank (Chicago Bank Helps); Hallmark (Pedestals); S.C. Johnson Shout (America's Learning); S.C. Johnson Clean & Clear (Baby, Floors of America, Two to One, Clear Choice); Sears (Car Stereo--Little Old Lady, Tires--Return to Valley, Mufflers--Torture Test 19.99 Rev.); Sherwin-Williams (Subway Sale); Speed Queen (Numbers)]
    [Honig Cooper & Harrington: Home Savings & Loan Association (Wedding Reception, Fly Tying, Dining); Crave cat food (Building Package)]
    [Jennings & Thompson: Arizona Biltmore (It's Your Resort, Too); Circle K food stores (The Easy Way); Cudahy Foods (Introducing Extra Lean)]
    [Los Angeles: Albertson's (Gold Coast, Price); Hunt Wesson Reddi Wip (Lookie Here/Pie, Eeek/Strawberries, Heh/Ice Cream, Yikes/Gelatin), ORE Ida/Heinz Deep Fries (Closer); Sunkist (Navel, Pick of the Crop); Winchell's (Unforgettable Sweepstakes)]
    [New York: Clairol Frost & Tip (Designer Cap); Coca-Cola Milkmate (Singing); Frito Lay corn chips (Father Munchter); Frito Lay Lights (Light Up); Sears 13th Month sale (Everything You Wanted, You Shouldn't Have); Sears Fashion Place (Soft & Pretty); Sears Bras & Girdles (Fit as a Fiddle, Operator, Magic Trick); Western Electric corporate (Wally, Wedding); Lorillard Hong Kong/Middle East--Kent (Circleline, Central Park, Rooftop Cafe, Around New York (French), Horse Farm (Arabic))]
    [San Francisco: C&H Sugar (Preferred Stampede, Mamas); California Raisin (Jingle Rev.); Clorox 2 (Mr. Red); Formula 409 Spray (Special Mess); Soft Scrub (Letters, New House); Twice As Fresh (Goodbye Harry); Castle & Cooke/Dole Pineapple (Big Table); Idaho Potato Commission (Hemingway); Levi Strauss jeans (Needle Nose); Pacific Telephone Directory Assistance (Our Son)]
  - FCB 14. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301476 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 16. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301475 (Box AV1)
    [Chicago: Hallmark (Clowns, Kaleidescope, Party Ideas, Improvisations, New Dimensions); Kraft (Family Reunion, I Remember); Sears (Trackside); Sherwin-Williams (Woman Scrubbing Sale); Sunbeam (Roller Coaster, Parlez Vous Gourmet]
    [Honig Cooper Harrington: Kal Kan Mealtime (Tails in Motion, 1000 Words Mature, Tails Out Mature); Las Vegas Hilton (Revolution)]
    [Jennings & Thompson: Valley National Bank (Affordable House/PCL, Banking Card/Restaurant)]
    [Los Angeles: Mazda GLC (Hotel, Auto Show); U.S. Forest Service Fire Prevention (Because of You, Dummy)]
    [New York: Clairol (Miss Clairol Extra Magic, Son of a Gun Movie); Western Electric (Something New, In Your Hand); Fritos (San Jose)]
    [San Francisco: C&H Sugar (School, Grocery Store); Clorox Bleach (Choice Mask); Levi Strauss (Gorilla)]
  - FCB 17. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301474 (Box AV1)
  - FCB 18. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301473 (Box AV1)
  - Series B: SFF1 001-052, SFF2 001-049. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301472 (Box AV1)
  - Series C: NYF. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 20:00, 301471 (Box AV1)
  - Series D: LA film Heinz. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 20:00, 301470 (Box AV1)
  - Series E: CHV1 (45 spots). Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301469 (Box AV2)
  - Series F: CHF1 001-033 (Chicago Office). Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 20:00, 301468 (Box AV2)
    [S.C. Johnson: Step Saver (Sniff Test, Half Time); Future (Growing Bottle); Clean & Clear (Clear Choice, Two To One Vs. Mop & Glo, Floors of America, Baby); Gloss 'n Toss (Really New, Gloss 'Em All, One for All, Can Do For You, Ragman). Wilton (I Did It). Kraft: Corporate (Family Reunion); Caramels (Betcha, Apple Tree); Barbecue Sauce (Cowpokes). Pizza Hut (Let Yourself Go Lunch, Let Yourself Go When, Let Yourself Go When--Couples, Supreme National). Armour Dial Tone Soap (All Together Feeling, Americana montage, Bike Hike, Body, Bomp Bomp, Put On revised, Put On/New Shape, Dial Smile, Good Day, Gymnast, Hello Goodbye, Maybe, Memories--Little Boy, Moms, Mr. Inside/Mr. Outside, New Dial Morning, 100%, 100% revised, Pick Up--Truck, Teacher, Volkswagen, Volleyball, Wedding). Sherwin-Williams Interior Paint (Woman Scrubbing, Subway/Sale). Hallmark: Greeting cards (Friendship/Presenter, Birthday/Presenter); Games (Jockey); Small Gifts (Gift Center I). Zenith color televisions (Worker/Color Sentry, Pete Rose, Zenith Presents Survey, Golfer/Color Sentry, Breakthrough Blueprint, Breakthrough, Simple Truth/Color Sentry, Simple Truth Tuner). Speed Queen (North Dakota, Coal Miners, Gremlins)]
  - Series G: CHF2 076-105 (Chicago Office). Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301467 (Box AV2)
    [Sears: Diehard (Saturday Night); batteries, shocks, filter change (Stop Sign); Diehard (Indy Sales); car stereo (Little Old Lady); muffler (Only Muffler); Diehard, air filter (Sellout/Dirty); muffler (Surprise, Reader); Diehard (Trackside); tires, shocks (Super Road Handler); Diehard (Good Old Charlie, Anchorage People); muffler (Torture Test); Diehard (Independence Hall, Lives Up To Its Name); 48-Month battery (What A Way); shocks (Blazing Saddles); stereo (If You've Got); motor oil (Beat That Deal); tires, oil (Silent); shocks (Metric); muffler (Torture Test); Road Handler (Steady Rider, Chitwood, Pony Express); tires (Metric Price Guide, Newspaper Line, Nice Guys, 77 Sale); snow tires (Return to Valley); tires (Truckin'); heavy duty shocks (Tire Sale); battery (Guardsman Belted); tires, shocks (Line Up, Free Installation, Metric Line-Up, Rural Roads); shocks (Rural Roads revised/Dynabelt 25); tires (Tune Up School, Graduate); Pong Telegram (Grandpa); muffler (Only Muffler); shocks (Globe 1/2 Price); Road Handler, shocks (Super Road 1/2 Price revised); bikes (Boston to Philly); Pinball (Wishes); shoes (Dynamite Savings, Granny revised)]
  - Series G: CHF3 139-151 (Chicago Office). Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301466 (Box AV2)
    [Sears: shoes (Magical Speakers, Kaleidescope revised, Vignettes); shocks (48-Month Heavy Duty Shocks); tires, oil (Flag Wave, XSS70 Savings/Filter Change). S.C. Johnson: wax (Car Sale Or Sale Car); Raid (I Can Do It Myself, Bet Your Life, Serious alternate, Inside Walls, Spelling Bug, Stunt Flyers, Bowling Ball revised, The Door); Wax (Big Deal); Off (Mini Golf, Car Wash); Deep Woods Off (Babe Winkelman, Winkelman Minn.); Raid (Sniper II, Tommy, Flying Squadron, Bowling Ball, Casino); Pro Strength (Pro Label); Roach Tape (Old Yellers); Yard Guard (Poolside revised); Raid (You've Never Seen Full Strength, Serious original); Shout (Oh Oh version I, I'd Shout It Out, Before You Answer, America's Learning, Line Up, Got Something Better, Surprise, But You're Supposed To Say, What Would You Do, I'd Shout It, Donut, Hallelujah revised, Jerry's Deli, Kid Presenter, With The Plumber)]
  - 2nd Q78 Domestic material only. 1978. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301465 (Box AV2)
    [Chicago: First National Bank (Count On It, Three Years); IBC/Butternut Bread (Show-n-Tell); S.C. Johnson (Be Fresh--With the Plumber, Rain Dance--Musical Doors II); Kraft Barbecue Sauce (Cowpokes); Kraft Macaroni & Cheese (I Like to Save Money, Makes Sense, San Francisco, New York, Glauster); Pizza Hut (Kids, Work, First Date); Sears (Tires--Truckin', Shoes--Dynamite Savings, Mufflers--Surprise); Sunkist orange soda (Surfing, Volleyball, Scooter)]
    [Jennings & Thompson: Diamonds (Father's Day, Manhattan, Le Soft); Circle K (Cars, Fast Foods/Hot Dogs); Valley National Bank (Wedding)]
    [Los Angeles: Albertson's Supermarket (Meat/Color, Meat/Fat, Real Bakers, Fruit/Vegetables); Knudsen (Cottage Cheese--Beautiful, Yogurt--Wake Up); U.S. Forest Service Fire Prevention (Rita Racoon); Mazda RX-7 (RX-7 Intro)]
    [New York: Clairol (Skinvention--My body, Loving Care--Old 'n Grumpy, Miss Clairol--My Sculpture); Sears sportswear (Buy a Tee); Frito Corn Chips (Little Girl); Kent/Lorillard Hong Kong (Chinatown 60, Chinatown 30, Rowboat, Horse Farm 60, Horse Farm 30, Penthouse); Plough (Supershade--Highest, Tropical Blend--Savage Tan); Sears (Everything Summer/Closets, Everything Summer/Hands Full, Pantyhose Fit As a Fiddle)]
    [San Francisco: Armour Dial Tone Soap (Sand Castle); Foster Farms chicken (Farm Fresh); Clorox Formula 409 spray (Start to Work)]
  - 3rd Q78 Domestic material only. 1978. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301464 (Box AV2)
  - Interstate Brands (Outstandwich, Baker Boy). 1976. Format: Umatic. TRT: 1:30, 301463 (Box AV2)
  - Interstate Brands, Butternut Bread. 1979. Format: Umatic. TRT: 1:30, 301462 (Box AV2)
    [Includes What Happens, Helper, Outstandwich]
  - Tape F, Lestoil. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301461 (Box AV2)
  - Noxell spots. Undated. Format: Umatic. TRT: 60:00:00, 301460 (Box AV2)
  - S.C. Johnson, Stepsaver. 1979. Format: Umatic. TRT: 1:30, 301459 (Box AV2)
  - NYF1. Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 10:00, 301458 (Box AV2)
  - Blue-collar men 20-32. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301457 (Box AV3)
  - Lite men. 1977 Apr. 19. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301456 (Box AV3)
  - Men 33-45 part 1. 1977 Apr. 14. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301455 (Box AV3)
  - Men 33-45 part 2. 1977 Apr. 14. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301454 (Box AV3)
  - White-collar men part 1. 1977 Apr. 20. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301453 (Box AV3)
  - White-collar men part 2. 1977 Apr. 20. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301452 (Box AV3)
  - Women Lite part 1. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301451 (Box AV3)
  - Women Lite part 2. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301450 (Box AV3)
  - Zenith, 1:30 PM, 1-7/8 one side. 1976 July 13. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301449 (Box AV3)
  - Zenith men. Undated. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301448 (Box AV3)
  - Hallmark Plant-by-Mail, 1:30 PM. 1976 Aug. 5. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301447 (Box AV3)
  - Hallmark Plant-by-Mail, 6:00 PM. 1976 Aug. 5. Format: 1/4 audiotape. TRT: 10:00, 301446 (Box AV3)
  - Mag. Sneakers. Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 10:00, 301445 (Box AV3)
  - FCB Los Angeles, unidentified reel. Undated. Format: 16mm. TRT: 10:00, 301444 (Box AV3)
  - Radio commercials. 1976 Nov. 4. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: C90, 301443 (Box AV3)
  - Ads--First tape. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: C90, 301442 (Box AV3)
- London Office records, 1948-1951; 2 boxes
  Case studies, research reports, portfolio of window displays.
  - Greek Tourism, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Public Relations Report on Behalf of the National Tourist Organisation of Greece, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Report on Behalf of Federation Horlogere Suisse, 1949-1950 (Box 5)
  - The Story of Toni Home Permanent Wave and an Explanation of Public Relations, 1948 (Box 5)
  - Window Displays Arranged by FCB on Behalf of the National Tourist Organisation of Greece, 1951 (Box 6)